World of Tomorrow is a animation, drama, science
fiction film directed by Don Hertzfeldt.
A little girl is taken on a mind-bending tour of her distant future.
Emily (voice), played by Julia Pott.
Emily Prime (voice), played by Winona Mae.
Simon (voice) (uncredited), played by Sara Cushman.
World of Tomorrow is a series of animated science fiction short films
written, directed, produced, animated, and edited by Don Hertzfeldt.
The series began with World of Tomorrow (2015), followed by World of Tomorrow Episode Two: The Burden of Other
People's Thoughts (2017) and World of Tomorrow Episode Three: The Absent Destinations of David Prime (2020).
The first film was nominated for Best Animated
Short Film at the 2015 Academy Awards.
All three films feature the voice of Julia Pott, frequently alongside Hertzfeldt's
four-year-old niece Winona Mae, who was recorded while drawing and playing.
Her spontaneous, natural vocal reactions and questions were then
edited into the stories to create her character.
Indiewire called the first film "one of the greatest short films in the history of movies," and Rolling Stone ranked World of Tomorrow #10 on its list of the "Greatest Animated
Movies Ever."
Of the "dreamy, beloved" ongoing series,The Film Stage noted, "Hertzfeldt has crafted what might be the crowning achievement of modern science fiction."
The film explores themes of future, virtual reality,
immortality, narration, time travel.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and mind_bending.